Hey Sophia. it's me.
You never answer your phone.
I wanted to talk to you before I leave.
Your sponsor called me.
She says she hasn't been to your meetings...
I'm worried about you.
I'm going to be spending the night
at the observatory.
Call me. please.
Doctor? Colonel Mokrani.
I'm your military liaison.
Nice to meet you.
What just happened in there?
You scared them.
Do you ski?
What? Do I ski?
Yes.
You work in the mountains...
So I was thinking...
It's possible.
Ah. I used to.
Not for a long time.
You okay?
Yes.
I hate these things.
My men are here to secure the site.
You must tell me if we get
in the way of your work.
Don't worry. I will.
The bill. please.
Come on. Sophia. Answer your phone.
What's going on?
Multiple objects are approaching Earth.
What sort of objects?
We don't know.
They're travelling at more than
a thousand kilometers per second.
That's impossible.
They're losing speed.
They're slowing down as they enter
the Earth's atmosphere.
Do you think it's an...
...an attack?
Impact in 80 seconds.
Impact in ten seconds...
...six. five. four. three. two...
Reports of multiple impacts...
Initial assessments
suggest the damage is localised...
Saaid. prepare the reports on the impacts
every ten minutes.
Yes. sir.
On all the sites.
Hey. little sister.
I wanted to see if you're okay.
I know you don't want to speak to me.
Just text me
to tell me you're okay.
Please.
Fuck! Answer your phone! Shit!
Why do you keep calling me?
I know things are bad between us...
I think you should come
and stay at the observatory.
Why?
It's safer here.
Do you think these things are dangerous?
I don't know. I don't know.
Please...
Come here.
For once. trust me.
But I don't understand.
Tell me what's happening.
You have petrol in your car?
Yes.
Tell me what's happening.
Don't take anything with you. just leave.
Now.
Catherine. I don't understand.
You're scaring me.
Sophia. Sophia. I beg you.
Okay.
The first samples show
at least four unknown elements.
What's generating the electromagnetic field?
All we know is that the frequency
and amplitude are continuing to increase.
We send probes to other planets
to study them. It's logical...
...that they might do the same to us.
Why send so many?
And why are they clustered
around population centres?
The original signal.
We picked it up during
one rotation of the Earth.
And?
It was the time needed to make
a complete scan of our planet.
They were mapping us?
Do you think we should destroy them?
They could be weapons.
The pictures from Wyoming.
Have a look.
An F16 dropped a one tonne bomb
on one of them.
Direct hit and not even a scratch.
The train station. please!
No. no. I'm not working.
What is that?
It's the effect of the electromagnetic field
on the atmosphere.
The British government has issued
a warning of an imminent attack.
Where are you?
On the road through the valley.
I'm stuck in traffic.
Listen to me.
There's going to be an attack.
You have to find somewhere to take shelter.
What do you mean. an attack?
I don't know. you need
to find shelter underground.
Just go!
There's nowhere to go!
I'm sorry for being such a screw up...
Don't say that. It's not true.
I never phone you back.
I'm a screw up.
You're always there for me.
Don't say that.
- You've got to get underground.
- But there's nowhere.
- Just go!
- The things I said to you. I'm sorry.
You've got to find an underground shelter.
Now! Go!
There's nothing! There's nowhere to go.
We've lost contact with our planes.
They're falling like flies.
Something is happening.
What's happening?
We need a connection. Quick!
Everyone take shelter.
Make sure all the doors stay closed.
You think it's all over?
I don't know.
Everyone!
Save your batteries...
...switch off your torches.